Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary?
Till someone proves it real.
Through it all.
Through all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there.
To stand by you.
Like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on the crew.
We are.
That looks like it's ready.
Momoo! Lunchtime! Momoo!
Where is he?
Kinda weird.
I've never seen Momoo
show up late to a meal.
I wonder what happened.
Conis!
The possession of weapons is a
clear affront to my authority.
As an example to any other
would-be rebels in this town,
I'm going to kill you right now so
they can see the fate that awaits them
No way,
that guy is insane He killed someone for
just having a weapon I won't land Hey,
wait,
don't go out there You have
absolutely no right to do this, Arlong
We've paid your tribute
without fail for over
eight years Why would
we rebel against it now?
Just think about it It makes no sense!
Now take your hand off Genzo!
Yeah!
It's not like he used the
weapons! That's right! Let him go!
Yeah, let Genzo go!
Hoarding weapons shows he was
planning a rebellion against me.
But, on the other hand,
I could destroy you all.
Please try to protect your friends so
you won't give me an excuse to do that.
Either way is fine, but
rebellions will not be tolerated.
Everybody just go home.
Do you want to waste all of our
work over the past eight years?
For what?
The time for you to give your lives for
this village was back when they first came.
Now we must continue to be patient.
The most important thing is
that we continue to live.
We swore we would not let them
defeat us as long as we're alive.
Gensang! No!
Well, Zed, I agree with you.
Here, it's good to know that even disgusting
insects like you enjoy being alive!
Oh, no.
There is no way any of you will ever come
close to the perfection of the Fistman!
Damn you! Don't move!
He wants you to attack.
We can't just stand here!
Your deaths will mean nothing.
You must continue to be patient.
Even if I die!
That's a good ending for you.
Pay close attention, humans.
This is what happens to those who defy me.
Even if it's inside their tiny heads!
Exploding stars.
What was that?
Up there, look.
There's someone on the roof!
Who the hell is that guy?
I am the great warrior of
the sea, Captain Usopp!
Usopp?
Also known as the Demon King Usopp,
feared and hated by almost half the world.
I command thousands of
men, loyal and vicious men.
That's the guy I told you about, the
one with the long nose and got away.
Bring on your thousands of men.
I'll crush them one by one.
The exploding star did
nothing, and now he's pissed.
Repulsive human.
What can a creature like you do to me?
Starlong, hold on just a second.
After losing Koza, we can't afford
to kill off any more tribute,
money!
Villages are fun to destroy, but
ruling over them makes us more money.
If we lose
some, we can always get more.
This man must reign to me!
He's destroying it all!
Usopp!
Am I dead yet?
He's not dead yet! Oh crap! Get him!
Get him and tear him apart.
Let's go back to Arlong Quark
before he destroys everything!
Yeah, I'm with you.
Don't let him get away.
Who does that jumpsunker think he is?
We'll be back.
You can all live for now!
I'm so sorry, everybody.
This has all been my fault.
What are you talking about?
You're not a fish man, are you?
Yeah, but who was that guy who attacked?
Hello, everyone.
It's good to be back home.
Nami?
It's Nami. You.
What's wrong?
You never just come walking
through Cocoyashi anymore.
I heard quite a commotion.
Arlong, huh?
I only have to get seven
million more berries.
Your already bad reputation
just keeps getting worse.
That's fine.
I am a pirate.
Arlong can be a very reasonable
guy when he wants to.
I just need a little more
money to finish our agreement.
Just seven million berries
shy of the 100 million gold.
You know it's really not that high a price
considering it's gonna
buy back our village.
She tells me to run but I've
got nowhere else to go but
here besides promised Luffy
I'd bring her back with me.
Man what's he up to because things
are getting messy around here?
That's mine I put it on my
plate that's how it works.
Sorry, how about you
eat this thing instead?
I wouldn't feed that
rotten slop to my dog.
Shh, quiet.
There's something down there.
It's big.
What the hell is that?
Sea monster!
It's a cow.
Not cow.
They don't swim.
A hippo?
Whatever it is, you can tell
it's from the Grand Line.
What is it doing all the way
out here in the East Loop?
Why is he staring at us?
He wants the food! What?
Clint, give it to him before
he sinks the ship! Gum-Gum!
Bad sea cow, stay away from our food! Ha!
Yes, you knocked it out!
Oh crap, you made it mad!
It's back for more!
Dumbass, there's no reason to
punch this poor, hungry hippo.
she's probably just a baby and can't
catch food for herself yet huh that right?
you're insane.
here you go, eat up.
don't be scared.
i won't hit you.
what the hell are you doing?
damn jerk.
it was gonna eat me with the plate.
what could i do?
stand back.
this is my show.
Oh, yeah, cool!
That's that.
Yes!
Back to the food!
That was refreshing.
You guys are insane. Seriously.
What's taking so long?
Luffy, where are you?
Five more minutes of this, and
I'll keel over from boredom.
Incredible!
What are you?
Some kind of super fish?
Not even the mighty Hachan!
Octopusnator of the Arlong Pirates
can pull you from the ocean!
What an epic battle!
I don't know who you are, but you're
the gutsiest fish in the East Blue!
Hey, what the...?
It was me all along?
You are indeed the gutsiest
fish in the East Blue, me!
Hold on, that's weird!
It sure is?
Hey, who are you?
Speak up now
Who? Me?
Well, I'm Hatchan, but all my friends
call me Hatchi Are you a fish man too?
Of course, of course, I'm
an amazing octopus fish man.
It looks to me like you're just a human.
Uh, yeah. A marine!
Or possibly a guest!
A guest?
Uh, you could say that.
Arlong isn't here, is he? No.
I thought you might know where he is.
Apparently, there's some long-nosed
guy running around causing trouble.
So Arlong locked up the
long-nosed friend here,
then went to Cocoyashi Village to
hunt down that pesky troublemaker.
Oh, man. Who's up?
Well, I guess I better save him.
It's Cocoyashi Village.
How do I get there? Get in!
You're a guest. Hop in.
I'll take you. Swordsman.
Oh, man.
I can't shake these guys.
Hey, where'd he go?
All those in favor of
leaving Usopp alone say aye!
Aye! Aye! Aye! Aye!
You fool, you're dumber than I thought.
Ah, you agree with me too! That's great!
Eggstar, special attack!
Oh, I think I'm gonna roll!
I guess fishmen aren't all
they're cracked up to be!
Not one of those scaly morons
can catch Captain Usopp!
Hehehe!
Huh? Hey! Huh? What?
Ah!
Yeah, I'm fine! Thanks for asking!
I made it down safe and
sound, as you can see!
Cocoyashi Village.
Orlong should be around here somewhere.
Oh, great, thanks!
No problem, bye now.
Oh, one more thing!
I completely forgot to ask you your name?
What do you mean?
We've been over this, I told you my name.
Hachan Nice to meet ya.
That was strange.
What the hell happened here?
Who did this to you?
What do you say?
Rolanoa.
Saru. What?
Pirate hunter?
Has he come to collect my head?
We had him.
That man we got, that was him.
He was Saru. That's him? Yes.
The swordsman was Rolanoa.
Two.
Ah Long, found him.
What is this?
Don't tell me that Zoro's...
Catching this scum isn't
enough to satisfy my hunger.
Oh yeah?
Well, then let me go.
Oh, and I'm sorry about earlier.
I was just saying hello.
That's how we do it in my village.
Longnose, you are one of Zoro's men
It's only natural for well-known
bounty hunters to come after me
Please don't kill me I don't have
anything to do with Zoro I promise,
please don't kill me Shoot,
enough of your cowardly lies
Even if you don't know Zoro,
you still stood against
Arlar You die either way
Okay, no more lies.
Zoro and I are like
brothers, partners for life.
If you so much as lay one of
your creepy webbed fingers on me,
he'll show up and kill you all.
Is that right?
So if I kill you, Zoro will show up?
No, no, that's not what
I was trying to say.
I was trying to say the exact opposite.
Killing me is bad.
If you keep me alive,
Zoro will show up, see?
What I want to know is how how did he
escape what do you mean what I mean is
someone let him escape
I think that somebody
has betrayed us perhaps it was Nami who
let him in so that bastard could take
your head now that you mention it she has
been acting strange lately yeah she Even
helped Zoro when you jumped into the water.
Don't tell me she was one who had Zoro
from this dive and tricked us all.
Don't forget, her chief
skill is deception.
Enough of this!
You should be ashamed.
This is pure conjecture.
Nami?
How dare you?
I swore I was a member of
this group eight years ago.
My loyalty is shown with this tattoo.
I'm sorry, Nami.
It's natural for you to be upset.
But you should know.
I don't suspect you of
anything treacherous, Nami.
I trust you.
After all, we've known
each other for eight years.
We're just a little on
edge right now, that's all.
Surely you can understand that.
We need to focus on Zoro and
his gang of bounty hunters.
Hey, Nami!
Say something!
Please, Nami!
He just had to go and do that.
What's wrong, Nami?
You're pale.
You feeling okay?
As for Longnose here, not
even you can save him now.
No not when he defied our long how long
how long will I be suspected of betrayal?
You're too clever for your
own good I'll have the amount
our long and I Agreed too
soon it doesn't make any sense
for me to betray you now
I know eight years ago you
agreed to purchase Cocoyashi
village for a hundred million.
and berries, but I just
can't figure it out.
You love nothing except money.
You betrayed your family
and your village for it.
So, why do you care for this village now?
This puny little heap of houses.
I thought long and hard about it,
but I found this in your room.
Can't be that's my what what do you
mean you're saying he was captured yeah
they took him back to Arlong Park just
a little while ago that courageous young
man stood up to Arlong and those
fishmen he's probably dead by now this is
bad they won't be forgiving he got
caught right right after my little visit.
Who's up? Hold on!
Yeah!
Faster to Arlong Park!
Nami, hang on!
As I watch the sun rise,
I begin to wonder What could be
the reason it's so hot inside?
No answer has come, but I can't
get away from what's true.
It's because of you!
Show me how to catch those feelings.
Get them to come back to me!
I'll do what I must.
Because they're everything I want to be.
Pass these arms around my dreams.
And pull them back from yesterday.
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we can make the way?